Sara-Jane Gibbs

UX Designer

Profile

I am a UX designer who aspires to create engaging products that ultimately help people in their day to day life.

My experience spans 9 years working in Ecommerce. Beginning in digital production for Arcadia Group, working directly on the delivery of digital products for Evans, before transitioning into UX Design. I am currently working for leading health and beauty retailer A.S. Watson Group, providing enhanced digital experiences for the inhouse brands, most recently, the website redesign for The Perfume Shop.

Contact

London

07837950449

Key Skills

User Research

User Journeys

Task Analysis

Accessibility

Wireframing

Prototyping

Interaction Design

Agile Methodologies

Stakeholder Management

Usability Testing

Presentations

Self Motivation

Communication

Teamwork

Information Architecture

User Flows

sarajanegibbs@gmail.com sarajanegibbs.co.uk

linkedin.com/in/sarajanegibbs

Experience

UX Design Specialist

Key Responsibilities:

- redesign, Checkout enhancements and Search.
- Produce UX Reviews of the websites to identify usability problems and provide recommendations.
- testing decisions on analytics and user research.

Key Acheivement:

Software

Axure

Adobe XD

Sketch

Invision

JIRA

HTML & CSS

Google Optimise

Google Analytics

UX Designer

ICX4 / July 2017 - December 2017

ICX4 work with leading banks to ensure that they have access to current and relevant customer data.

Key Responsibilities:

- Ownership of a project, designing wireframes for data profiles based on use cases (KYC, On-boarding, Compliance, AML).
- Worked closely with the User Researcher, ensuring designs fit the users needs, through testing with users, creating user journeys and verifying designs against use cases.
- Led design workshops to gain ideas on how data could be presented.

A.S. Watson Group / February 2018 - Present

A.S. Watson Group is the worlds largest international health and beauty retailer, with 12 retail brands in 25 markets.

- Work closely with the brand stakeholders, providing user flows, wireframes and prototypes for key projects, including; Website
- Run AB & MVT tests to help optimise the websites. Basing our
- Consult on projects being led by our inhouse brands, providing feedback and advice.

• Led the UX design for The Perfume Shop website redesign, using research and analytics to create solid wireframes and protoypes. Working closely with visual designers, developers and key stakeholders to ensure the redesign was delivered to a high standard.

Sara-Jane Gibbs

UX Designer

UXDI Teaching Assistant

General Assembly / June 2017 - July 2017

Having completed the User Experience Immersive course, I was asked to be a teaching assistant on one of the courses. Here, I was able to offer valuable support and advice to the students, deliver feedback on their projects, as well as support the course tutor.

UX Designer

Generation Success / April 2017

Working in a team, in a two week sprint, our goal was to redesign Generation Success' website. In this sprint, through user research, information architecture, wireframing, prototyping and testing we produced a high-fidelity responsive website design, design specification, final stakeholder presentation and wider site recommendations.

UX Designer

General Assembly / February 2017 - April 2017

A 10 week, full time immersive course learning and practising the UX design process. Throughout the course I worked on projects which covered user research, interaction and interface design, prototyping and testing, and working with clients.

Online Production Coordinator

Evans - Arcadia / May 2014 - February 2017

Key Responsibilities:

- Coordinated daily CMS builds of website content on desktop, mobile and apps.
- Management of two Production Assistants; responsible for their training and development.
- Worked closely with marketing and design teams to ensure that content was delivered on time.
- Worked closely with website development team to implement new site functionality.
- Worked with third parties to carry out Multivariate and A/B Testing

Key Achievements:

- Managed the implementation and launch of a new mobile platform for Evans. Working closely with development teams and Project Managers.
- Managed the relaunch of the desktop website, transferring data from one programme to another and thoroughly testing the customer experience.

Education

UXDI Course

General Assembly / February -April 2017

B.A Media Studies

De Montfort University / 2007 - 2010